<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Those who dance are considered insane by those who cannot hear the music]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Those who dance are considered insane by those who cannot hear the music]]></description>
        <link>http://music.jonnor.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 22:48:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://music.jonnor.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Subsignal – Beautiful & Monstrous]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Subsignal – Beautiful & Monstrous</h1><p>Subsignal emerged from the ashes after the german progressive metal band Sieges Even split up about a year ago.  On-board is lead vocalist from Sieges Evens last two albums ("Art of Navigating by the Stars" and "Paramount"), Arno Menses and the lead guitarist, Markus Steffens.  As I am a huge fan of those two album, this release was filled with both excitement and a bit of anxiousness. Will they try to do the same and fail? Will it be something entirely different? Awesome different or crappy different?</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.jonnor.com/2009/12/subsignal-beautiful-monstrous/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ebcd21bc-9540-4b36-9712-a89164b20d96</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 22:48:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sons of Seasons – Gods of Vermin]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Sons of Seasons – Gods of Vermin</h1><p>Sons of Seasons was founded by Kamelot keyboardist Oliver Palotai in 2007, and this is their debut album.  I actually did not know that until just now when I looked it up on Wikipedia, so this band was entirely new to me when I first hear this album back in June.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.jonnor.com/2009/12/sons-of-seasons-gods-of-vermin/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ad20b84c-4719-47c9-8366-96175a68c8e8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 22:23:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Musical Highlights of 2009]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Musical Highlights of 2009</h1><p>I originally planned on doing a post on some of my favorite albums of 2009.  But I was having some trouble picking out only a few, and I don't really want to limit myself to my favorites. So I'm doing a series of posts, showing some favorites, some disappointments and the occasional oddity (musical or otherwise). Consider it a kind a of Christmas/advent calendar, if you want.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.jonnor.com/2009/12/musical-highlights-of-2009/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4a12a8e6-1ef0-4e61-921e-bf4a8c7a9d55</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 22:22:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tragedy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Tragedy</h1><p>It's a tragedy, that some hide behind a mask. Pretending that everything is good, pretending to be someone else. It's a tragedy, that the mask is never dropped. Not for friends, not for family.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.jonnor.com/2010/06/its-a-tragedy/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">487e440c-ac67-4364-8b0b-6f4f63867963</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 22:29:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Musical highlights of 2009 – wrap up]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Musical highlights of 2009 – wrap up</h1><h2>Ups</h2><p>Have you ever basically completed an email but not sent it, forgot about it and then, when you remember it again, procrastinated on sending it because you didn't send it right away? Well, then you understand this post.  </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.jonnor.com/2010/01/musical-highlights-of-2009-wrap-up/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2109716b-9d65-4723-874f-cc31234ae74a</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 22:27:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Silent Stream Of Godless Elegy – Návaz]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Silent Stream Of Godless Elegy – Návaz</h1><p>I have a strong preference for music in a language I can understand, if nothing else than for the opportunity to mumble along. But "Návaz", the latest album from Czech band Silent Stream Of Godless Elegy, is a little gem, even if I can't understand a word of the Czech lyrics. Návaz, like the previous albums is a doom metal album with strong influences from Moravian folk music and lore. What I like most about this album are the heavy contrasts: Quick, playful violins against slow, drudging guitar riffs; soft female voice against harsh male voices; traditional folk instruments and musical themes against modern metal.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.jonnor.com/2011/09/silent-stream-of-godless-elegy-navaz/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a5e5b413-7a95-4212-97f7-a7459a5ce2fc</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 22:32:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Irepress – Sol Eye Sea I]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Irepress – Sol Eye Sea I</h1><p>This album is one of, if not the absolute favorite of mine this year. Which is surprising since it has nearly no vocals at all. Typically good vocals is almost a requisite for me liking an album. But these guys from Sharon, Massachusetts, USA pulled it off. An near-instrumental album that I not only liked but blew my mind.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.jonnor.com/2009/12/irepress-sol-eye-sea-i/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">88221869-9fd0-4bd7-8690-537bbec9fcb0</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 22:24:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Berlin concerts awesomeness]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Berlin concerts awesomeness</h1><p>A few weeks back I saw Gojira (warning: horrible flash based site, even the myspace page is better) at Knaack here in Berlin. While I hadn't listened to Gojira much before going, it was a great show. Nice venue, sound was good, kick-ass music and performance, and the crowd loved it. What more can you ask for? The event was promoted by a company called Trinity Concerts, and apparently they do a whole bunch of good stuff this autumn. Here are the ones I plan to go to between now and Christmas:</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.jonnor.com/2010/09/berlin-concerts-awesomeness/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">524c547b-0868-4e6a-89c6-d29963643ed1</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 22:29:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Free Spirit – Pale Sister of Light]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Free Spirit – Pale Sister of Light</h1><p>Whaaat, something not metal?  And no, I'm not gonna slaughter it. Cause I actually like it, and have in fact listened to it quite a bit. Yes, its cheesy as hell, and is nothing special far as musicianship go. But quite frankly, its catchy as hell and straight out rockin'. Can't resist it!</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.jonnor.com/2009/12/free-spirit-pale-sister-of-light/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">523244ec-058f-4e44-b9b8-7698896819d1</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 22:28:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lost in Thought – Opus Arise]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Lost in Thought – Opus Arise</h1><p>If you're a fan of traditional progressive metal, you might want to check out Lost in Thought s debut album: Opus Arise.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.jonnor.com/2011/08/lost-in-thought-opus-arise/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">339fea81-c555-458b-a17b-ee47c0e5e4fd</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 22:29:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>